TOP-NOTCH CREATIVE recipe



the method:

In a large pot, place a college grad seasoned with a passion for digital as well as traditional design. Add in an array of freshly picked skill-sets and bring to a boil. After 10 minutes, reduce heat and stir in a wide variety of clients and types of industries served. At this point, sprinkle in a pinch of sarcasm, a dab of humor, then cover and simmer slowly over the course of 15 years, while periodically adding a splash of Guinness and the occasional industry award. Served hot or cold, this recipe pairs well with any project, team or environment.

If you'd like to try this particular recipe and would rather not have to go through all the hassle, then simply call me and we'll create top-notch creative together instead.



jon toney

address

2304 w. 103rd terrace leawood, kansas 66206

phone

214 395 9016

email

me@jontoney.com

portfolio

www.jontoney.com

super secret portfolio

private.jontoney.com pass: shhhhhh

experience

intouch solutions

overland park, kansas (2008 - present) associate creative director

intouch solutions

overland park, kansas (2008 - 2008) senior art director

mmg world wide

kansas city, missouri (2007 - 2008) senior interactive art director

sibley peteet design

dallas, texas (2001 - 2007) art director, developer and information technology manager

rsw creative

dallas, texas (1999 - 2001) designer, manager of web development and information technology

seven world wide

dallas, texas (1998 - 1999) design consultant, data management and technical support

clocktower studio

edmond, oklahoma (1998) designer/art director

education

university of central oklahoma bachelor of arts & science (1997)

technical skills

applications

adobe creative suite, quarkxpress and apple final cut pro

programming & scripting

strong html and css skills, a solid familiarity with both javascript and javascript frameworks, while also maintaining a comfortable working knowledge of php, ruby, python and .net

low-f

number 2 pencil, paper, technical pen, adhesive spray and x-acto knife

martial arts

five-point-palm-exploding-heart technique

affiliations

former member and volunteer of the dallas society of visual communications (dsvc)